

Respectful self-motivator at finding reliable solutions for software issues. Experienced in programming and offering skills. Complex problem-solver with analytical and driven mindset. Dedicated to achieving demanding development objectives according to tight schedules while producing impeccable code.

ALMOND RAE TUAZON

CONTACT

PHONF. 0949-858-9490

https://github.com/MondSE

WFBSITF:

https://www.atuazon.xyz

azirtuazon@gmail.com

TECH STACK

- Programming Knowledge
 - C#
 - C++
 - \triangleright Java
 - PHP
 - MySQL
 - MongoDB
 - JavaScript
 - ReactJS
 - HTML
 - \triangleright **CSS**
 - Git.
- Microsoft Office Knowledge
 - Word
 - Excel
 - **Publisher**
 - Access
 - PowerPoint
- Multimedia Knowledge
 - Figma
 - Photoshop
 - After Effect
 - Premiere Pro
 - Illustrator
 - OBS

EDUCATION

Global Knowledge Academy

2015 - 2017

PROFILE

Associate Degree in Computer Systems Servicing

AMA Computer College

2019 – Undergraduate

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science major at System and Software Engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

Global Knowledge Academy (GKA) – Computer System Servicing [Intern] September 2016 – December 2016

- Demonstrated Respect, Friendliness and willingness to help wherever needed.
- Adaptable and proficient in learning new concepts quickly and efficiently.
- Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems specially on networking.
- Skilled at Working independently and collaboratively in a team environment.
- Perform minor repairs to equipment and arrange for other servicing needs.
- Respond to user requests for service, troubleshoot problems and help develop solutions.
- Support PC hardware components, desktop operating system software, and application software.

City Government of Angeles (ACTDO) - Data Analysis [Office Worker II] October 2017 – June 2020

- Strengthened communication skills through regular interactions with
- Completed paperwork, recognizing discrepancies and promptly addressing for resolution.
- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions.
- Gained extensive knowledge in data entry, analysis and reporting.
- Managed time efficiently in order to complete all tasks within deadlines.
- Applied effective time management techniques to meet tight deadlines.

City Government of Angeles (ACTDO) - System Developer [Office Worker II] July 2020 - December 2022

- > Learned and adapted quickly to new technology and software applications.
- Researching, designing, implementing and managing software programs
- Testing and evaluating new programs
- Identifying areas for modification in existing programs and subsequently developing these modifications
- Writing and implementing efficient code
- Determining operational practicality
- Developing quality assurance procedures
- Deploying software tools, processes and metrics
- Maintaining and upgrading existing systems
- Working closely with other developers, UX designers, business and systems analysts